<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>East Valley Real Estate Video Blog with Kenny Klaus</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Kenny Klaus Team is to be your best resource for East Valley real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Kenny Klaus Team, your professional East Valley Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:37:38 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:37:38 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s Happening in Our October Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/R60K-rxT7gc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s plenty of noise out there about our current real estate market. So today we wanted to cut through it and share what’s truly happening in our local market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news is that we’re still seeing a very healthy market overall. &lt;strong&gt;The market continues to favor sellers, but it’s beginning to slow down somewhat.&lt;/strong&gt; The end of March and early April was the peak of the multiple offers and bidding war chaos. That’s still happening, but not as much as it was before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interest rates remain low, and we anticipate they’ll stay that way through this year and hopefully into the next. However, with the way the world is these days, you never know what changes may happen. The top five real estate economists have predicted that within the next five years, we should see a gradual downturn in appreciation. We predict to see somewhere in the mid-fours and upper-threes within the next five years. In my opinion, that’s great news because the housing market is stable. You should also know that &lt;strong&gt;mortgage payments are very affordable compared to rents in this market.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we have an array of people moving here because of the large companies coming here to the East Valley. There’s a new Facebook data center, Apple, Gateway, the Legacy sports complex, and more. They’re bringing more jobs, which brings more people. I think we’ll continue to see an excellent market in Phoenix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re still seeing a very healthy market overall.%20http://localhost:4000/whats-happening-in-our-october-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re still seeing a very healthy market overall.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve considered buying a second property, &lt;strong&gt;a slew of people are sitting on quite a bit of equity today, which is money just sitting there not working for you.&lt;/strong&gt; The investment market is very strong at the moment; we’re undersupplied on rentals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re here every day working hard and ensuring we’re keeping up with the latest technologies and tools to best serve you. We appreciate your continued support and referrals; they’re the lifeblood of our business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know there’s a bunch of information and programs out there, so if you have questions about them or anything having to do with real estate, call us first. We work with those programs and can guide you through all your different options and help you decide what’s best for yourself and your family.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 15:23:52 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-happening-in-our-october-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-happening-in-our-october-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stay Up to Date on All Things Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ySpkg8B7McM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our continuing effort to bring value to the trusted people in our network and to help you stay on top of everything that’s happening in our market, &lt;strong&gt;we’ve started a podcast called the &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://state48homeowner.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;State 48 Homeowner Podcast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There, you can not only find out what’s going on in the real estate industry at large but also get home maintenance tips, advice about mortgages, and information about how to maintain your home’s value for the future. You can scroll through our database of shows and pick one that strikes your interest. Feel free to share with your friends and family, too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market is always changing, but the media that report on it are often weeks or months behind what’s going on in real-time, so &lt;strong&gt;the State 48 Homeowner Podcast is just one way to stay on top of all things real estate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check it out when you get a chance! And if you ever have any questions or ideas for topics that we could address in our podcast, don’t hesitate to reach out to us via phone or email. We’ll always give you our professional advice and put your best interest at heart.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 15:53:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/stay-up-to-date-on-all-things-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/stay-up-to-date-on-all-things-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Want to Be Your Go-To Real Estate Resource</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/a5LGmRJowc0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today’s message is brief but important: We’re here for you.&lt;/strong&gt; There’s a lot going on in the market, in the media, and the world at large. If you see something strange in the news, have any questions about the market, or just want to better understand a concept related to real estate, we can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a buyer or a seller, we understand all the programs out there and understand if those are tools we can use. &lt;strong&gt;If for some reason we can’t offer you a product or program, we’re going to tell you that, and we’re going to point you in the right direction. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We will act in your best interest at every possible turn.%20http://localhost:4000/we-want-to-be-your-go-to-real-estate-resource.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We will act in your best interest at every possible turn.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re ultimately acting in your best interest at every turn. If you’re considering selling your home to an iBuyer, for example, we can help you run the numbers, examine the pros and cons, and help you make a smart, informed decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer programs like our Buy First, Then Sell Program, Instant Offer Program, Sell-and-Stay Program, and more. A lot of our clients have taken advantage of these programs, and we’d be happy to help you take advantage of them as well. &lt;strong&gt;There are many tools out there to help you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ever have any questions or any real estate needs, give us a call first. We’ll help you assess the situation from a professional perspective and point you in the right direction, ultimately acting in your best interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need anything, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email today. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 14:38:57 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/we-want-to-be-your-go-to-real-estate-resource.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/we-want-to-be-your-go-to-real-estate-resource.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A St. Patrick’s Day Market Update</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uyurvsphb9c?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy St. Patrick’s Day! Today I’m just sharing some quick information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may have heard how crazy our market currently is due to low inventory. Buyers are having a difficult time finding new homes because there are multiple offers on most properties. Our team has helped over 40 buyers get under contract already this year. &lt;strong&gt;There’s no luck involved—it’s pure skill.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve been doing this for over 20 years; we have strategies and tools that help our client’s offers stand out from the rest and help them win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Our team has helped over 40 buyers get under contract already this year.%20http://localhost:4000/a-st-patricks-day-market-update.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Our team has helped over 40 buyers get under contract already this year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a house to sell and you’re concerned that you won’t find one to buy, our Buy First and Sell program is the right tool for you. We’ve had dozens of clients take advantage of this program; &lt;strong&gt;you don’t sacrifice your equity.&lt;/strong&gt; You move into your new property first, prepare your other home for sale, list it, and then get top dollar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give us a call or send an email for more details about how we can help you buy or sell or if you have any questions. We’d love to provide a free consultation with no hassle or obligation. Enjoy St. Patrick’s Day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-st-patricks-day-market-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-st-patricks-day-market-update.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trust Us With Your Real Estate Needs</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_QyIa-UUKXE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Super Bowl week! However, there’s a more important game going on out there—the real estate game. &lt;strong&gt;We want to make sure you’re receiving your real estate information from a good, reliable source.&lt;/strong&gt; There’s so much going on in the market: low inventory, low interest rates, and tons of talk and noise. We’re always here to be your trusted resource in real estate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re here in the trenches every day conducting business, and people are still buying and selling real estate. We have excellent strategies to help buyers get into their new homes; we win more contracts than the average real estate agent. We also have strategies to help make the selling process go as smoothly as possible for our sellers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re always here as your trusted source in real estate.%20http://localhost:4000/trust-us-with-your-real-estate-needs.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re always here as your trusted source in real estate.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re considering taking advantage of the current market but are worried about finding a new house because of the low inventory—you’d be surprised. &lt;strong&gt;Properties come up for sale all the time, but you need to be in a position to jump&lt;/strong&gt; when the right one appears. We have a Buy First, Then Sell program where you won’t have to give up your equity; we’ll find your new home first, secure it, move in, then prepare your first house for the market. We also have a Sell and Stay program as well as Lease Purchase programs for those who are trying to get into the market but can’t quite purchase yet. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t ever hesitate to reach out to us via phone or email if you have questions about buying, selling, or anything else. Also, &lt;strong&gt;contact us if you want an update on your home’s current market value straight from us&lt;/strong&gt;—not from some iffy online site. Additionally, we always have home service referrals for when you need something done in your house. Enjoy the Super Bowl!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/trust-us-with-your-real-estate-needs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/trust-us-with-your-real-estate-needs.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Why Is Now the Perfect Time to Sell?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LCt5GN3S40M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current real estate market is unlike anything I’ve ever seen in my 21 years in the business. Inventory is at an all-time low, so if you’re thinking of selling or would like to know what your home is worth, you’d be surprised at what price you can fetch. Get in touch with us and &lt;strong&gt;we’d be happy to give you a true home valuation.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking of selling and buying but are afraid to do so because inventory is so low, I have great news: Now that we’re into 2021, we have more programs than we’ve ever had that allow you to pull off these simultaneous transactions. I truly wish we had some of these programs in the past to make the process of buying and selling real estate easier. We realize that not everyone fits into the same category—we have programs for those looking to buy and sell at the same time, sell and then stay in their home to release some of their equity, lease their next property so they can buy it within the next five years, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With interest rates as low as they are, buyer demand is high&lt;/strong&gt;, so we’d love to have a quick conversation with you to outline your options. As always, you’re under no obligation; we’re here to serve you. We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 18:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-why-is-now-the-perfect-time-to-sell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-why-is-now-the-perfect-time-to-sell.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: What Can We Do To Help This Holiday Season?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3m-K_pXRA-k?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On behalf of the entire Klaus Team, I wish you happy holidays! Once again, thank you all for an amazing year. Despite all the chaos going on in our world, the real estate market has remained very steady, anchored by low interest rates and low inventory. We’re grateful for this resilient market, and we’re excited to be turning our attention toward making the holidays brighter for a few families in our community. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are heading into the fifth year with our charity, Klaus Team Cares. For every person you refer and every home you buy or sell with us, we take a portion of that commission and donate it back to Klaus Team Cares, allowing us to then give back directly to local communities. This year we’re serving 24 families (84 total kids) that were brought to our attention as needing some assistance for Christmas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We commissioned a group to do all of the shopping for these families, and we held a wrapping party last Saturday. &lt;strong&gt;We’re ready to make this holiday season special for our neighbors who are experiencing hardship in these especially trying times.&lt;/strong&gt; Our effort to give back is merely an outpouring of our deep appreciation; we’re so thankful for your continued support and your referrals, which allow us to do so much good here in the local community. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This year we’re serving 24 families (84 total kids) that were brought to our attention as needing some assistance for Christmas.%20http://localhost:4000/q-what-can-we-do-to-help-this-holiday-season.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This year we’re serving 24 families (84 total kids) that were brought to our attention as needing some assistance for Christmas.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who receive our local newsletter, you’ll be able to read about some additional ways that you can help us support our community. For example, you’re always welcome to drop off your nonperishable food donations at our office, Monday through Friday, and we’ll be sure to get it to our partners at the United Food Bank. Also, from 11 a.m. to 7 p.m. every Wednesday this month, we’ll be at the Fry’s in Guadalupe and Signal Butte ringing bells for the Salvation Army. &lt;strong&gt;On Wednesday, December 9, the Klaus Team Cares charity will match any donation that is made to the Salvation Army.&lt;/strong&gt; Stop by and drop your donation in one of the kettles, or donate by visiting &lt;a href=&quot;https://klausteamcares.org/&quot;&gt;klausteamcares.org&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you for all that you do for us here at the Klaus Team. 2020 hasn’t been an easy year for most of us, but it’s inspiring to see everyone pull together. People still need to buy and sell homes in our area, and we’re proud to serve not only them, but their friends and family as well. We look forward to an amazing 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have more specialized programs now than we’ve ever had before, including Buy First Then Sell, which has opened up possibilities for so many families. It allows you to buy and move into your new home first, then get your old home ready for market and sell for top dollar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in learning more about any of the Klaus Team’s game-changing solutions for buying or selling in today’s market, please reach out via phone or email. &lt;strong&gt;We’re always here to be of service,&lt;/strong&gt; and we look forward to hearing from you. Stay safe, and have a fantastic holiday season!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 11:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-what-can-we-do-to-help-this-holiday-season.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-what-can-we-do-to-help-this-holiday-season.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are You Using the Homebot Tool?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wnn1SyavVWs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that 83% of the average American’s wealth at retirement comes from home equity and not other investments? This means that &lt;strong&gt;making&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;smart home finance decisions over the life cycle of homeownership is the key to building long-term wealth.&lt;/strong&gt; How can you ensure you’re making the right decisions at the right time? Allow us to introduce you to Homebot, a personalized dashboard that helps homeowners build wealth by making smart and timely home finance decisions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every month, Homebot automatically sends you an easy-to-read home overview that tracks your home value, loans, equity, and your local real estate market conditions. It provides information like when to remodel, refinance, buy, and sell. It’s like a report card for your house. Homebot even helps you calculate the financial impact of converting a property into a short-term rental on Airbnb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Every month, Homebot automatically sends you an easy-to-read home overview.%20http://localhost:4000/are-you-using-the-homebot-tool.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Every month, Homebot automatically sends you an easy-to-read home overview.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;U.S. homeowners leave over $100 billion of wealth on the table each year by making poor home finance decisions.&lt;/strong&gt; The constant fluctuation of real estate markets makes these decisions challenging. That’s why Homebot makes decisions simple, customizing the experience to your market and situation. It empowers you with the knowledge you need to build wealth. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the Klaus Team, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klausteam.com/homebot/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Homebot is 100% free to homeowners!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You can even share it with your friends, family, and social sphere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about Homebot or real estate in general, call or email us. We at the Klaus Team would love to help with whatever you need.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 15:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-you-using-the-homebot-tool.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/are-you-using-the-homebot-tool.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Do You Feel Homeownership Is Out of Reach?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LoWMLIl82kU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to create long-term memories in a home, but aren’t ready to purchase yet? &lt;strong&gt;We at the Klaus Team are excited to introduce our Lease to Own program, a new way to rent first then buy.&lt;/strong&gt; Here’s how it works: First, we help you qualify for the right program; we have multiple solutions with flexible income and credit requirements to accommodate your specific situation. Next, you’ll choose a new home you love that’s listed for sale (most single-family homes and townhomes qualify), and our partner will purchase the property on your behalf. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the purchase is completed, you move in as a tenant and begin paying rent; you can lease anywhere from two to five years. In some cases, a percentage of rent goes toward your down payment. Finally, &lt;strong&gt;you may choose to buy the home during your lease term, or, you can simply walk away at the end of the lease.&lt;/strong&gt;  When you choose to purchase, you begin building equity and wealth. We have more solutions than ever before to help people transition into a new living space. Reach out to us today by phone or email and we’ll get you started on the path that’s best for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klausteam.com/lease-to-own/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.klausteam.com/lease-to-own/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 16:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-feel-homeownership-is-out-of-reach.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-do-you-feel-homeownership-is-out-of-reach.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Have You Heard About Our Newest Program?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wD_V4fPaI_4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here at the Klaus Team, we’re proud to introduce our &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klausteam.com/buy-then-sell/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Buy Then Sell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; program, a new way to buy a house before selling your old one. &lt;strong&gt;Here’s how it works:&lt;/strong&gt; First, we get you approved for a home loan so you can make a stronger offer on the house you love. We’ll even lend you the down payment on your new home; that means no worrying about having equity tied up in your old house. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve purchased your new home, we advance you up to six months of mortgage payments on the old house so you’ll never have to pay two mortgages at the same time.  Finally, we offer you up to $25,000 in prepaid home prep funds so you can sell your old house for top dollar. &lt;strong&gt;With a dedicated support team, we’re there for you every step of the way&lt;/strong&gt; to ensure your house sells as quickly as possible. We’ve spent a lot of time improving the real estate experience to give you more certainty, convenience, and cost savings, and we believe that’s what makes our Buy Then Sell program the best possible way to buy and sell a home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out more by contacting a Klaus Team agent by phone, email, or visiting our &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klausteam.com/&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. We’d be more than happy to answer your questions and get you on the path to a smooth transaction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 16:38:18 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-have-you-heard-about-our-newest-program.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-have-you-heard-about-our-newest-program.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
