<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>East Valley Real Estate Podcast with Kenny Klaus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Kenny Klaus Team - your professional East Valley Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Kenny Klaus</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-12-13 12:38:55 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Kenny Klaus</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>klausteam@klausteam.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Kenny Klaus</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the East Valley Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Kenny Klaus Team - your professional East Valley Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Highlights From Our Client Appreciation Event</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/highlights-from-our-client-appreciation-event.html</link>
        
          <category>Events</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-10 14:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We had a blast on December 1 when we invited our past clients to join us and our special guest, Santa Claus, to a private screening of the #1 movie in America, “Ralph Breaks the Internet.” We hope to see you at our next event!

Attached are some photos from the event.


</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Every year, the Klaus Team celebrates our clients and their families by renting out a theatre at the Harkins Superstition 25 movie theatre.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Every year, the Klaus Team celebrates our clients and their families by renting out a theatre at the Harkins Superstition 25 movie theatre.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Rick Collins</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/rick-collins.html</link>
        
          <category>Our Agents</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-03 17:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Rick has lived in Arizona since 1975 and been in Real Estate since 2008. He has a wife of 25 years and two kids in college. In his free time, he enjoys golf and hockey. Having flipped roughly 100 homes, Rick has extensive experience with updating and rehabbing properties. This makes Rick a valuable asset for our investor clients as well as our buyers and sellers looking to improve their properties before or after sale.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Meet Rick Collins - Buyer Agent</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Meet Rick Collins - Buyer Agent</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Christine Matthews</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/christine-matthews.html</link>
        
          <category>Our Agents</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-03 17:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I am originally from Queens, NY and have lived in Arizona since I was 5 years old.  I have 2 sons that are 31 and 17.  I was in banking for almost 19 years including Chase Bank for 15.5 years.  I worked in trust department, consumer lending, home equity lending and business lending where I was a loan officer, underwriter and SBA underwriter.  I’ve been a Realtor for 14 years, all with Keller Williams Integrity First, and with The Klaus Team for 8 years as a transaction manager, working with buyer, sellers, and short sale and HUD transactions.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Meet Christine Matthews - Realtor/Transaction Manager</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Meet Christine Matthews - Realtor/Transaction Manager</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are We in a Real Estate Bubble?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-we-in-a-real-estate-bubble.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-03 11:29:57 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Are+We+in+a+Real+Estate+Bubble%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Are we in a real estate bubble? I’m here to answer this question today.

We are certainly seeing changes in the market right now and things are shifting. We saw interest rates increase several times this year, and we may see them increase three more times in 2019. However, let’s keep things in perspective. Right now, rates are right around 5% on average. From 2009 to 2011, they were over 6%.

Overall, the housing market has continued to be solid. We’re seeing a bit of a slowdown, to be sure, and a slight decrease in home appreciation. That’s not necessarily a bad thing, however. There are still more people moving here than there are moving away. Things are changing, but we’re definitely not in a bubble.

“We should continue to see a solid, stable market for the next few years.”

We’ve been working on some programs with our lenders and sellers to offer a bit of an incentive to still get people qualified for a home affordably. We’re always at the forefront of this and looking out for the best interests of our clients.

We’re still in a very good market and hope to continue to see a solid, stable market for the next few years.

One thing I wanted to note is that if you’re currently moving or considering a move and you need to donate some things, the Salvation Army has a great program where they’ll come and pick up everything and donate it to a great cause.

If you have any questions about the market or about real estate in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Are+We+in+a+Real+Estate+Bubble%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Are+We+in+a+Real+Estate+Bubble%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’ve been getting a lot of questions about a potential bubble in the real estate market. Here’s what you need to know.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’ve been getting a lot of questions about a potential bubble in the real estate market. Here’s what you need to know.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Andi Ravenscroft</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/andi-ravenscroft.html</link>
        
          <category>Our Agents</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-21 11:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Always give more!

My clients are the source of everything I do. Always giving more and providing value through creating lasting relationships. It is an honor when clients become friends. I pride myself in being authentic by giving you the good, the bad, and ugly news with solutions through the entire process.

A house is a large investment that becomes a home with endless memories. Your time and goals are always a focus for me. As a professional, my role is to understand and study your interests to be in the strongest negotiating position possible.  

As a transplant to Arizona coming from South Dakota and Oregon, I appreciate the sun and the unique beautiful scenery it has to offer year-round. My background is in executive operations in senior living administration with a Bachelor’s Degree in Healthcare Business Administration from Oregon State University. That experience provides an understanding of unique business acumen and how to best support your goals with creativity. Outside of my real estate passion, I enjoy experiencing the world with my husband, Eric. In my off-time, I volunteer with the Ronald McDonald House Central and Northern Arizona Charities and local non-profits.

Andi RavenscroftSenior Real Estate SpecialistNursing Home Administrator - ORKlaus Team - Silver Group - Keller Williams Integrity First RealtyMobile:480.825.4005Office:480.354.7344Linkedin profileHome Search site:https://andi.klausteam.com/Address: 2919 S Ellsworth Rd #133 Mesa AZ 85212Free senior living resources inquiry:https://www.klausteam.com/silver/

My business is built on your referrals!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Meet Andi Ravenscroft!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Meet Andi Ravenscroft!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Business Spotlight: Just-In Time Moving and Storage</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/business-spotlight-just-in-time-moving-and-storage.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-12 15:11:56 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Business+Spotlight-+Just-In+Time+Moving+and+Storage.mp4</guid>
        <description>

On today’s “Business Spotlight,” we’re featuring Just-In Time Moving and Storage—a great local resource for anyone planning a move.

To give you all a better idea of how Just-In Time Moving and Storage can serve your needs, we met with owner Justin Hart for a discussion about his business.

“We’ve worked very hard over the last 13 years to make sure we provide solutions for all different types of moves. So whether you’re moving locally, across town, across the street, or across the nation, Just-In Time Moving and Storage is fully capable of helping you with your move,” said Justin when asked about his business’ services.

And beyond helping with your move itself, Just-In Time Moving and Storage also offers short- and long-term storage in their climate-controlled warehouse. Their ultimate goal is to make your move easier, whether that means moving just a few items or transferring everything you own.

“Whether you’re moving locally, across town, across the street, or across the nation, Just-In Time Moving and Storage is fully capable of helping you with your move.”

According to Justin, the difference between his and other similar businesses is that Just-In Time Moving and Storage offers “quality men, quality trucks, and quality equipment.”

Any move with Just-In Time will be smooth, but Justin also advises that those planning a move follow a couple key steps ahead of time to make your transition even easier. The first thing Justin recommends is to stay organized and get rid of any belongings you no longer want. This way, you aren’t paying to move items you don’t want or need.

The second piece of advice Justin shared is to plan ahead. His company books up very quickly. So if you’re looking to hire them, make sure to reach out well in advance.

If you’ve got moving or storage needs Justin and his team can help with, give Just-In Time Moving and Storage a call at (480) 213-0395 or visit www.jitmoving.com.

And, as always, if you have any other questions for us at the Klaus Team, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Business+Spotlight-+Just-In+Time+Moving+and+Storage.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Business+Spotlight-+Just-In+Time+Moving+and+Storage.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>On today’s “Business Spotlight,” we’re featuring a great company that can help handle all your moving needs: Just-In Time Moving and Storage.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>On today’s “Business Spotlight,” we’re featuring a great company that can help handle all your moving needs: Just-In Time Moving and Storage.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s Going On in Our Arizona Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-our-arizona-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-26 12:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Whats+Going+On+in+Our+Arizona+Market%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

It’s time for another market update, and we’ve seen some interesting changes since the last time we examined local real estate trends.

First, as you may already know, our overall Arizona market has been very strong in 2018 with respect to appreciation and sales. However, as predicted, rising interest rates have now caused an increase in inventory—and this has led to a slight slowdown in our market. This isn’t necessarily a bad thing, though.

In essence, this change simply means that sellers will need to be especially cognizant of their pricing strategies. And buyers, too, can reap certain advantages by making their move in today’s market. For instance, even though interest rates have increased, they are still historically low. This means buyers still have the opportunity to lock in a favorable rate before the Fed makes even more increases—as is expected to be the case as we head into 2019.

“Whether you’re looking to buy, sell, or invest, there are opportunities available right now for you.”

The bottom line is that our market is beginning to balance out. We’ve been in a seller’s market for some time, but conditions have started to level off.

Overall, there’s a lot happening in our Arizona right now. Whether you’re looking to buy, sell, or invest, there are opportunities available right now for you, and our team would be happy to help you with any of these goals.

Even if you aren’t ready to make a move immediately, we would still like to help you stay informed. We offer a number of great events, and we highly encourage you to come out and expand your knowledge of real estate. You can find more information about our team and the events we offer by visiting our website:www.klausteam.com.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Whats+Going+On+in+Our+Arizona+Market%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Whats+Going+On+in+Our+Arizona+Market%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How has our Arizona market changed recently, and how will these changes impact your real estate goals? Check out today’s market update to find out.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How has our Arizona market changed recently, and how will these changes impact your real estate goals? Check out today’s market update to find out.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Miss Our Next Homeowner Workshop</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dont-miss-our-next-homeowner-workshop.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Kenny Klaus</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-09 15:59:03 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Dont+Miss+Our+Next+Homeowner+Workshop.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our recent homeowner workshops have been massively successful, and it’s been very interesting to see the responses of those who have attended.

Our tips on preparing homes for the market, in particular, have been extremely well-received. If you’re curious about buying or selling, or simply want to better understand our market, I would highly encourage you to check out our next workshop. You will learn which upgrades and repairs bring the greatest return on investment, as well as a number of other things you can do to boost your chance of success in the market.

And if you have already attended one of these events, I would still encourage you to join us again. In addition to covering some of the basic information I mentioned earlier, we will also be covering current market trends. Our goal is to keep you informed as our market develops, so that you can be successful with your own buying or selling experience.

“We want to help you stay educated and up-to-date on all things related to local real estate.”

There is a lot of conflicting information out there about our market and about real estate in general. These workshops are designed to help you separate fact from fiction. We want to help you stay educated and up-to-date on all things related to local real estate. If you’re interested in attending our next workshop, click here for more information.

And, as always, if you have any other questions or would like to schedule a private consultation, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Dont+Miss+Our+Next+Homeowner+Workshop.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Kenny+Klaus/Videos/The+Klaus+Team-+Dont+Miss+Our+Next+Homeowner+Workshop.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Would you like to learn more about our local market? If so, we’d like to invite you to join us at our next homeowner workshop.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Kenny Klaus</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Would you like to learn more about our local market? If so, we’d like to invite you to join us at our next homeowner workshop.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in East Valley, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Kenny Klaus</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Kenny Klaus</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Kenny Klaus Team - your professional East Valley Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
